<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://bookerycommunity.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://bookerycommunity.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-10-12T01:33:43+00:00</updated><id>https://bookerycommunity.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Bookery</title><subtitle>The Bookery is a large community of over 1000 members focused around all things written word. Created in 2020 by Zachary Montgomery and Benjamin Hollon, we are dedicated to the creation, consumption, admiration, and discussion of literature. </subtitle><entry><title type="html">Starting a Blog</title><link href="https://bookerycommunity.com/reading/blog/bookery/2020/08/16/starting-a-blog.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Starting a Blog" /><published>2020-08-16T14:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2020-08-16T14:00:00+00:00</updated><id>https://bookerycommunity.com/reading/blog/bookery/2020/08/16/starting-a-blog</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://bookerycommunity.com/reading/blog/bookery/2020/08/16/starting-a-blog.html">&lt;p&gt;Hey there! Welcome to The Bookery’s blog. This will be a place where we can share our thoughts on reading and writing. We may also write about other topics on occasion, but most often it will be about reading or writing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We don’t have a set schedule for posts, we’ll just post when we have something to post about! This ensures all our content is quality-made and genuine, rather than made to fit a schedule. However, because of this uncertainty we highly recommend you sign up for our mailing list, which will send you an email whenever we release a new post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be on the lookout for our upcoming posts! We have some exciting things planned, especially now that we’ve gotten things sorted behind the scenes. I know this has been quite a short post, but I just wanted to say hey and welcome you to the beginning of what is sure to be a great part of our community.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Zachary Montgomery</name></author><category term="reading" /><category term="blog" /><category term="bookery" /><summary type="html">Hey there! Welcome to The Bookery’s blog. This will be a place where we can share our thoughts on reading and writing. We may also write about other topics on occasion, but most often it will be about reading or writing.</summary></entry></feed>